sunshinestatenews.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy | Sunshine State News

**About SunshineStateNews.com**

SunshineStateNews.com ("SSN") is an online news service.  SunshineStateNews.com cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [info@SunshineStateNews.com](mailto:info@SunshineStateNews.com).

**Information Collection and Use by SunshineStateNews.com**

**-Non Personally Identifiable Information**

SSN logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, operating system type, web browser type, the domain name of your service provider, the web pages you have visited, the content you have accessed, the advertisements you have been shown and/or clicked on and browser type, from visitors to the site.  This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services.

**-Use of Non Personally Identifiable Information**

This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members.  Visitor IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

**-Personally Identifiable Information**

SSN may permit visitors to submit content (including blogs, news stories, etc.), vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. In the course of these various offerings, we often seek to collect from you various forms of personal information. Examples of the types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, birthday, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a letter to our editors, a posting to a blog or a discussion board), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.

We may use your email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the news service.  Visitors may choose not to receive email of this type by following the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any e-mail you receive from this site.

We may also use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to offer you products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our sites, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information.

From time to time, SSN or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on SunshineStateNews.com.  Visitors may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate.  We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from.  It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**Use of Cookies**

SunshineStateNews.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and other information.  We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.  You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from SunshineStateNews.com in order to use most functions on the site.  Please note that SSN allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer.  Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Sunshine State News Privacy Policy.

**Links**

SunshineStateNews.com contains links to sites.  SSN is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites.  When linking to another site a visitor should read the privacy policy stated on that site.  Our privacy policy only governs information collected on SunshineStateNews.com.

**Chat Rooms, Journals and Blogs, Message Boards, and Public Forums**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, WebLogs, Message Boards, or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

SSN visitors may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Manage Your Profile and Personal Data page. SSN reserves the right to delete user accounts at any time for violations of this privacy policy or the Terms of Use. Users may not delete their accounts, but after a reasonable time of inactivity, the account may be deleted by SSN staff. ****

**Email Choice/Opt-out**

Visitors who no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may choose not to by logging into his or her account and un-checking the boxes for receiving the newsletter or news alerts. This is found in the edit section of the 'My Account' page. All notification emails and SunshineStateNews.com newsletters also include the above instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future.

**Third Party Advertising**

SSN reserves the right to implement or remove third party advertising at any time.  Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to visitors by SunshineStateNews.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies.  These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement.  In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on.  This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.  This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by SSN and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Security**

SSN visitor accounts are secured by member-created passwords. SunshineStateNews.com takes precautions to ensure that visitor account information is kept private.  We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to visitor information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff.  While the site does use very secure protection measures, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of visitor account information.  Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time.  For any additional information about the security measures we use on SunshineStateNews.com, please contact us at [info@SunshineStateNews.com](mailto:info@SunshineStateNews.com).

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information SSN Collects**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Sunshine State News will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by SSN, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the SSN Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. SSN reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of SSN or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest.  For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy.  If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it.  A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted.  If, however, we are going to use visitors' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [info@SunshineStateNews.com](mailto:info@SunshineStateNews.com) 336 E. College Ave Suite 201 Tallahassee, FL 32301.
